A Guide to the Office of the Dean of Students Office Administrative Files, 1950-2000
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Dean of Students Office Administrative Files 1950-2000
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-18/2/1.971
This collection consists of 20,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions apply only to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library in 1997 August.
Scope and Content Information
Topical files from Dean Robert T. Canevari's office, including the files of the Associate Deans and Assistant Deans of Students.
Organization
Series I: Dean of Students, Robert T. Canevari Boxes 1-11
Series II: Associate Dean of Students, Sybil R. Todd/V. Shamim Sisson Boxes 11-14
Series III: Assistant Dean of Students, Women's Leadership Development Boxes 15-17
Series IV: Assistant Dean of Students, General Information Boxes 17-22
Series V: Assistant Dean of Students, Greek Life Boxes 22-35
Series VI: Associate Dean of Students, Annette Gibbs/Ronald Stump Boxes 35-47
Series VII: Restricted Files Box 48
Contents List
- Series I: Dean of Student,Robert T. Canevari
  - Administrative Council 1993 (Box 1)
  - Blagden Committee 1994 (Box 1)
  - Task Force on Campus Violence 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Budget--ODOS, Resident Staff, Student Activities Business Manager 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Pep Band Review 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Pep Band Permanent File 1986-1990 (Box 1)
  - Ivy Road Design Study 1993 (Box 1)
  - Council on Community 1993 (Box 1)
  - Historic Renovation Corporation 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Lawn Steering Committee 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Madison House--25th Anniversary Committee 1994 (Box 1)
  - Master Planning Council 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Transportation/Parking Committee 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Pavilion VII Committee 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - School of Commerce 1988-1990 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Residential Life 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Residential Colleges 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Residential Colleges: Monroe Hill College Sub-Committee 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Residential Colleges: West Main Street Sub-Committee 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Search Committee for Vice President for Student Affairs 1993 (Box 2)
  - Student Housing Task Force (2 folders) 1993 (Box 2)
  - Substance Abuse Studies Council 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Task Force on Campus Violence--Violence 1993 (Box 2)
  - Task Force to Evaluate Alcohol and Other Drug Policies and Procedures, Status of Recommendations 1992 (Box 2)
  - Virginia ABC Board Correspondence (Restricted) 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Alcohol and Drug Brochure 1990 (Box 2)
  - Alcohol Awareness 1990-1993 (Box 2)
  - Affirmative Action 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association Miscellaneous 1991-1994 (Box 2)
  - University Architect--High Density Study 1992 (Box 3)
  - Athletic Department 1991-1993 (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Addenda Request, ODOS 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - Budget for Newcomb Hall 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - Budget--ODOS Programs 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Office of the Director 1990-1993 (Box 3)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1990-1993 (Box 3)
  - President's Convocation (Orientation) 1989-1993 (Box 3)
  - Cultural Resource Center 1993 (Box 3)
  - Office of the Senior Vice President and Chief Financial Officer 1989-1993 (Box 3)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Alan Leffers, Intern 1994-1995 (Box 3)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Wendy Leech, Practicum 1994 (Box 3)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Rachel L. Spector, Practicum 1994 (Box 3)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Lisa Guernsey 1993 (Box 3)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Laura Smith, Intern 1993-1994 (Box 3)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: William M. Fornadel 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Anne Barsanti, Practicum 1984 (Box 3)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Jamelle A. Smith, Practicum 1991 (Box 3)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Dana Smith, Intern 1990 (Box 3)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Marilyn Jefferson 1989 (Box 3)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Countess Hughes, Practicum 1987 (Box 3)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Tara S. Brown, Practicum 1986 (Box 4)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Mary Albergotti, Practicum 1985 (Box 4)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Lisa K. Bookman, Practicum 1983 (Box 4)
  - ODOS Interns/Practicums: Ronn Bonheur, Practicum 1982 (Box 4)
  - ODOS--Memos to Staff 1983-1993 (Box 4)
  - ODOS--Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1993-1995 (Box 4)
  - ODOS--Self-Governance Proposal: A Pilot Program for August 1993 (Box 4)
  - ODOS--Mid-year Retreat 1993 (Box 4)
  - ODOS--Letters of Success 1990 (Box 4)
  - ODOS--Annual Report, Robert T. Canevari 1992 (Box 4)
  - ODOS--Dean Canevari's Speeches 1992-1994 (Box 4)
  - Charlottesville/Albemarle Miscellaneous 1990-1994 (Box 4)
  - Development Office 1990-1993 (Box 4)
  - Dining Services 1989-1993 (Box 4)
  - Exit Interviews 1993 (Box 4)
  - General Faculty Miscellaneous 1990-1992 (Box 4)
  - Council for the Arts 1992 (Box 4)
  - Founders' School 1994 (Box 4)
  - Blacks in Greek Organizations 1991 (Box 5)
  - Fraternities Miscellaneous 1993-1994 (Box 5)
  - Fraternity Alumni Council 1993-1994 (Box 5)
  - North Grounds/Darden/Law Project 1992 (Box 5)
  - Finals 1992 (Box 5)
  - Class Trustees Program 1990 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1994 (Graduating Class) 1994 (Box 5)
  - Honor Loan 1991-1994 (Box 5)
  - Lambeth Fire 1994 (Box 5)
  - Housing Division 1992-1993 (Box 5)
  - Endowed Rooms 1962-1993 (Box 5)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council 1991-1994 (Box 5)
  - Inter-Sorority Council 1989-1993 (Box 5)
  - Support Plan Review Group (10 year Academic Plan) 1990-1992 (Box 5)
  - Incentive Pay Plan 1994 (Box 5)
  - Parents' Weekend 1992-1994 (Box 5)
  - Newcomb Hall--Cavalier Daily 1990 (Box 5)
  - The Lawn--Miscellaneous 1992-1994 (Box 5)
  - ISAS Meeting 1992 (Box 6)
  - Plan for the Year 2000--Priorities and Capital Campaign Costs 1992 (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles (2 folders) 1993-1995 (Box 6)
  - Lower Lawn Reservation Requests 1992-1994 (Box 6)
  - Leadership 2000 1994 (Box 6)
  - WTJU 1990-1993 (Box 6)
  - Cavalier Communications 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Newcomb Hall Renovation 1994-1995 (Box 6)
  - Newcomb Hall Director 1993-1995 (Box 6)
  - Robert Canevari, Interim Vice President for Student Affairs 1993-1994 (Box 7)
  - Ten Year Plan (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 7)
  - 1990-1992 Biennial Evaluation and Planning for 1992-1996 Preliminary Biennial Budget 1994-1996 (Box 7)
  - Resident Staff 1993-1994 (Box 7)
  - RACE--Race Relations, Philip Morris Grant Proposal 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - New (Hereford) College 1991-1994 (Box 7)
  - Judiciary Committee 1993-1995 (Box 7)
  - Stillfried-Godsey Memorial Scholarship 1994-1995 (Box 7)
  - Franz Stillfried Memorial Scholarship 1993-1994 (Box 8)
  - Resident Staff Serious Incident Reports 1993-1995 (Box 8)
  - Committee on Residence Staff 1990-1993 (Box 8)
  - Student Legal Defense Fund (Bailbondsmen) 1986-1990 (Box 8)
  - Residence Staff: Language Houses 1993 (Box 8)
  - Registrar's Office 1992-1994 (Box 8)
  - Student Health, Department of 1990-1993 (Box 8)
  - President's Retreat 1993 (Box 8)
  - Recommendations (Other than Students) 1992-1993 (Box 8)
  - Monroe Hill Residential College 1991-1994 (Box 8)
  - Residence Life Office 1990-1995 (Box 8)
  - President's Retreat 1994 (Box 8)
  - Racial Awareness Meetings--Provost 1993 (Box 8)
  - William W. Harmon, Vice President for Student Affairs (2 folders) 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - Parents' Committee 1993-1994 (Box 9)
  - Student Organizations--Miscellaneous 1993-1995 (Box 9)
  - Solicitations 1988-1993 (Box 9)
  - Date and Acquaintance Rape 1986-1991 (Box 9)
  - Sexual Assault--Miscellaneous 1991-1993 (Box 9)
  - Honor Committee (Restricted) 1993-1995 (Box 9)
  - Women's Center 1990-1993 (Box 9)
  - University Relations--Crisis Management Seminar 1991 (Box 10)
  - University Relations 1988-1993 (Box 10)
  - Pavilion XI 1991-1993 (Box 10)
  - University Union (2 folders) 1993-1995 (Box 10)
  - Student Council (2 folders) 1993-1995 (Box 10)
  - Campus Crime and Safety Conference Mar. 1993 (Box 10)
  - University Police 1990-1994 (Box 10)
  - Student Taxi Program 1993-1994 (Box 10)
  - Yellow Cab Bursar Referrals (2 folders) Nov. 1993 (Box 11)
- Series II: Associate Dean of Students, Sybil R. Todd/ V. Shamim Sisson
  - Leadership 2000 (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 11)
  - Leadership 2000 1994 (Box 12)
  - Leadership 2000 Manual 1993-1994 (Box 12)
  - Leadership 2000 Operations 1994-1995 (Box 12)
  - Leadership 2000 Folder 1995 (Box 12)
  - Student Officers 1985-1990 (Box 12)
  - TSPA Program (3 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 12)
  - Non-traditional age (TSPA) Information 1994 (Box 13)
  - First-Year Seminar 1990-1991 (Box 13)
  - First-Year Seminars--Exit Interviews--Instructors 1991 (Box 13)
  - First-Year Seminar Group Discussion 1991 (Box 13)
  - First-Year Seminar Participant Evaluations 1990-1991 (Box 13)
  - First-Year Seminar 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - Evaluations--First-Year Seminar 1992 (Box 13)
  - Exit Interviews--First-Year Seminar 1991-1992 (Box 13)
  - First-Year Seminar 1993 (Box 13)
  - First-Year Seminar--Instructor Evaluations 1993 (Box 13)
  - First-Year Seminar--Participant Evaluations 1993 (Box 14)
  - First-Year Seminar--Exit Interviews 1994 (Box 14)
  - First-Year Seminar 1994 (Box 14)
  - First-Year Seminars--Participant Evaluations 1994 (Box 14)
  - Parents' Weekend 1994 (Box 14)
  - President's Weekend 1993 (Box 14)
  - Parents' Weekend Leftovers 1989-1991 (Box 14)
  - Orientation Survey--NT-TSPA 1994 (Box 14)
- Series III: Assistant Dean of Students,Women's Leadership Development
  - Women: What We Are and What We Can Become--April 20th Brunch 1990 (Box 15)
  - Women's Leadership Program 1990 (Box 15)
  - Women's Leadership Project 1990-1991 (Box 15)
  - Women's Leadership Program 1991 (Box 15)
  - Women's Leadership Registrations 1992 (Box 15)
  - Women's Leadership Program 1992 (Box 15)
  - Women's Leadership Conference 1992-1993 (Box 15)
  - Women's Leadership 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Women's Leadership Conference (4 folders) 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Women's Studies' Executive Board 1991 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Assault--President's Faculty/Student Committee 1992 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Assault--Education Coordinator Advisory Board 1992 (Box 16)
  - Women's Self Esteem 1993 (Box 16)
  - Women's Leadership Development 1994-1995 (Box 16)
  - Women's Leadership Development 1994-1995 (Box 17)
  - Student Affairs Staff Development 1992-1993 (Box 17)
  - Women Administrators, Selected 1994 (Box 17)
- Series IV: Assistant Dean of Students,General Information
  - UJC Cases Pending (Restricted) 1991-1994 (Box 17)
  - Travel Expenses 1988-1996 (Box 17)
  - Transfer Students, Fall 1993 (Box 17)
  - Television Press n.d. (Box 17)
  - Task Force to Evaluate Alcohol and Other Drug Policies and Procedures 1991 (Box 17)
  - Survivor Booklet 1992 (Box 17)
  - Summer Staff 1993 (Box 17)
  - Substance Abuse Committee Working Group 1994 (Box 17)
  - Study Group on Drug Free Schools and Campuses Amendment 1990 (Box 17)
  - Student Health n.d. (Box 17)
  - Student Council 1991 (Box 17)
  - Student Affairs Staff Development Committee (2 folders) 1989-1992 (Box 17)
  - Stewart Howe Alumni Service 1990 (Box 18)
  - Speakers 1992 (Box 18)
  - UK Teaching Fellowships Selection Committee 1994 (Box 18)
  - University Committee on Sexual Assault and Judicial Review 1990-1993 (Box 18)
  - University Committee on Sexual Assault and Judicial Policy 1992-1993 (Box 18)
  - Women's Center Development Board 1992-1993 (Box 18)
  - Women's Center Coordinating Committee 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Glee Club 1994 (Box 18)
  - ACE/VIP Women's Seminar 1994 (Box 18)
  - V.I.E.W. 1989-1991 (Box 18)
  - Venable Neighborhood Association 1986-1991 (Box 18)
  - V.C.P.A. 1993-1995 (Box 19)
  - V.C.P.A. Fall Workshop Oct-94 (Box 19)
  - V.C.P.A Spring Retreat Feb-94 (Box 19)
  - Vacation Schedule 1992-1994 (Box 19)
  - UPD 'Hoos News 1996 (Box 19)
  - University Union 1986-1994 (Box 19)
  - Unity Leadership Conference 1993 (Box 19)
  - United Kingdom Fellowship Program 1993 (Box 19)
  - Women's Center Development Board 1991-1993 (Box 19)
  - Women's Center Development Council 1991-1992 (Box 19)
  - On Target Selections Process 1994 (Box 19)
  - On Target--Selected (Restricted) 1995-1996 (Box 19)
  - On Target--Not Selected (Restricted) 1995-1996 (Box 19)
  - ODOS 1989-1995 (Box 19)
  - On Target--Masters 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Off Grounds Party Policy 1993 (Box 20)
  - Personnel Policies 1989-1991 (Box 20)
  - President's Retreat (4 folders) 1989-1992 (Box 20)
  - Press 1994-1995 (Box 20)
  - Recommendation Letters 1996 (Box 20)
  - Relationship Groups--Together and Alone n.d. (Box 20)
  - Residence Life 1986-1994 (Box 20)
  - Risk Management 1991-1995 (Box 20)
  - Ropes Course 1991 (Box 20)
  - SACS Accreditation 1992-1993 (Box 20)
  - SACSA 1990-1995 (Box 20)
  - SACSA--Greenville, SC 1993 (Box 20)
  - SACSA 1988-1989 (Box 20)
  - SACSA 1989-1990 (Box 21)
  - SACSA Nominations and Ideas 1991 (Box 21)
  - SACSA Newsletter Articles 1985-1993 (Box 21)
  - SACSA Executive Council (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - SACSA Annual Conference - Birmingham, AL 1991 (Box 21)
  - SACSA--Interest Sessions Subcommittee 1994 (Box 21)
  - SACSA--Printed Programs 1980-1994 (Box 21)
  - NASPA 1991-1995 (Box 22)
  - NASPA Region III Presentation 1988-1990 (Box 22)
  - NAWE 1992-1995 (Box 22)
  - F/S National Correspondence 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Jefferson Society 1990 (Box 22)
- Series V: Assistant Dean of Student,Greek Life
  - National Pan-Hellenic Council 1990 (Box 22)
  - Alpha Delta Phi 1990-1993 (Box 22)
  - Newcomb Hall Party Policy 1993-1995 (Box 22)
  - National Fraternity/Sorority Officers--Scholarship Reports Handouts 1989 (Box 22)
  - National Interfraternity Conference 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - Alpha Delta Pi 1990-1993 (Box 22)
  - Alpha Phi 1990-1993 (Box 23)
  - Alpha Chi Omega 1990-1993 (Box 23)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi 1990-1993 (Box 23)
  - Alpha Omicron Pi 1990-1993 (Box 23)
  - Alpha Xi Delta 1990-1993 (Box 23)
  - Alpha Tau Omega (formally Tau Epsilon Phi) 1990-1993 (Box 23)
  - Chi Phi 1990-1993 (Box 23)
  - Chi Omega 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Beta Theta Pi 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Delta Sigma Theta 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Delta Sigma Phi 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Delta Gamma 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Delta Delta Delta 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Chi Psi 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Omega Psi Phi 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Kappa Sigma 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Kappa Delta Sorority 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi 1990-1993 (Box 24)
  - Kappa Alpha 1990-1993 (Box 25)
  - Delta Zeta 1990-1993 (Box 25)
  - Delta Tau Delta 1990-1993 (Box 25)
  - Delta Upsilon 1990-1993 (Box 25)
  - Phi Gamma Delta 1990-1993 (Box 25)
  - Phi Delta Theta 1990-1993 (Box 25)
  - Phi Beta Sigma 1990-1993 (Box 25)
  - Phi Mu (2 folders) 1990-1993 (Box 25)
  - Phi Kappa Psi 1990-1993 (Box 25)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha 1990-1991 (Box 26)
  - Pi Beta Phi 1990-1993 (Box 26)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa 1990-1993 (Box 26)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma 1990-1993 (Box 26)
  - Phi Eta Sigma (2 folders) 1989-1991 (Box 26)
  - Delta Epsilon 1990-1993 (Box 26)
  - Alpha Chi Omega n.d. (Box 27)
  - Alpha Phi 1991 (Box 27)
  - Beta Theta Pi 1992 (Box 27)
  - Chi Psi 1990 (Box 27)
  - Delta Upsilon 1988 (Box 27)
  - Gamma Phi Beta 1985 (Box 27)
  - Kappa Sigma 1991 (Box 27)
  - Theta Delta Chi 1990-1993 (Box 27)
  - Pi Kappa Phi 1990-1993 (Box 28)
  - Pi Lambda Phi 1990-1993 (Box 28)
  - Phi Mu 1989-1991 (Box 28)
  - Phi Delta Theta n.d. (Box 28)
  - Zeta Tau Alpha 1990-1993 (Box 28)
  - Zeta Psi 1990-1993 (Box 28)
  - Zeta Phi Beta 1990-1993 (Box 28)
  - Zeta Beta Tau 1990-1992 (Box 28)
  - Saint Anthony Hall--Delta Psi 1990-1993 (Box 28)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon 1990-1993 (Box 28)
  - Sigma Alpha Mu 1990-1993 (Box 28)
  - Sigma Chi 1990-1993 (Box 29)
  - Sigma Gamma Rho 1990-1993 (Box 29)
  - Sigma Kappa 1990-1993 (Box 29)
  - Sigma Phi 1990-1993 (Box 29)
  - Sigma Sigma Sigma (2 folders) 1990-1993 (Box 29)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon 1990-1993 (Box 29)
  - Sigma Pi 1990-1993 (Box 29)
  - Sigma Nu 1990-1993 (Box 29)
  - Zeta Tau Alpha n.d. (Box 30)
  - Theta Chi (2 folders) 1990-1993 (Box 30)
  - Safety and Security 1991 (Box 30)
  - Honor Committee 1994-1995 (Box 30)
  - SACSA Program--Integrating Career Day and Academic Advising 1983-1985 (Box 30)
  - SACSA: Higher Education in China 1987 (Box 30)
  - SACSA--Birmingham, AL 1991 (Box 30)
  - Historic Renovation Corporation (Board of Directors Meeting--Documents) 1986-1995 (Box 30)
  - ISAS--Institute for Substance Abuse Studies 1989-1994 (Box 30)
  - Jefferson Park Avenue Neighborhood Association 1988 (Box 30)
  - Judiciary Committee 1989-1994 (Box 31)
  - Honor System Study 1990-1991 (Box 31)
  - Mission Statement - Division of Student Affairs 1994 (Box 31)
  - Madison House--Personnel Committee 1995 (Box 31)
  - Madison House--Holiday Sharing 1995 (Box 31)
  - Madison House--Evaluation Committee 1993 (Box 31)
  - Historic Renovation Corporation 1996 (Box 31)
  - Historic Renovation Corporation--Newspaper Clippings 1985 (Box 31)
  - Historic Renovation Corporation--Non-Discrimination Statements 1986 (Box 31)
  - HRC Prospectus 1983 (Box 31)
  - HRC Corporation Correspondence 1988-1989 (Box 31)
  - Historic Renovation Corporation 1994 (Box 31)
  - Biennial Evaluation and Planning 1990-1994 (Box 31)
  - Leadership Program Results 1994 (Box 31)
  - Housing 1993-1994 (Box 31)
  - Historic Renovation Corporation 1990-1995 (Box 31)
  - Madison House Board 1992-1995 (Box 31)
  - Collaboration Virginia 1989 (Box 32)
  - Greek Officer Orientation 1989 (Box 32)
  - IFC--Interfraternity Council 1989-1993 (Box 32)
  - IFC Rush 1985-1993 (Box 32)
  - ISC--Intersorority Council 1989-1993 (Box 32)
  - FAC--Fraternity Alumni Council 1989-1993 (Box 32)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Correspondence 1991-1993 (Box 32)
  - IFC/ISC Trash Invitation to Bid 1992-1993 (Box 32)
  - How to Succeed as a Volunteer Board Member in Fraternity Management n.d. (Box 32)
  - Hazing Correspondence 1988-1993 (Box 32)
  - The Greek Report 1990-1991 (Box 32)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Volunteer Opportunities 1991 (Box 32)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Scholarship 1989 (Box 33)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Resources 1992-1994 (Box 33)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Residential College 1991 (Box 33)
  - Party Patrol On-Call Nightly Reports 1992-1994 (Box 33)
  - Party Patrol On-Call Nightly Report Forms 1991-1993 (Box 33)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Press 1987-1993 (Box 33)
  - GCC Subcommittee--Community Relations 1994 (Box 33)
  - Greek Coordinating Committee--GCC Extension Subcommittee 1993-1994 (Box 33)
  - GCC Subcommittee on ISC Sorority Growth n.d. (Box 33)
  - Fraternity/Sorority Party Management 1987-1992 (Box 33)
  - IFC/ISC Surveys--Statistics n.d. (Box 33)
  - IFC/ISC Correspondence 1988-1990 (Box 33)
  - ISC Rush 1987-1990 (Box 34)
  - ISC Goals 1987-1988 (Box 34)
  - ISC Correspondence 1987-1990 (Box 34)
  - Greek Coordinating Committee 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - Greek Letter 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - IFC Rush 1990 (Box 34)
  - IFC Correspondence 1987-1988 (Box 34)
  - IFC Judiciary Committee 1988-1990 (Box 34)
  - ISC Forum: Alumnae--National 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - FAC Subcommittee on Positive Pledge Programs and Hazing 1992 (Box 34)
  - Fraternities/Sororities--Alcohol 1992-1993 (Box 34)
  - Fraternity/Sorority--Disabilities 1992 (Box 34)
  - Fraternity/Sorority--Educational Programs 1993 (Box 34)
  - Fraternity/Sorority--Expansion 1989-1994 (Box 34)
  - Fraternity/Sorority--Fire and Safety Inspections 1988-1993 (Box 34)
  - Fraternity/Sorority--Fundraising 1994 (Box 34)
  - Fraternity/Sorority--House Directors 1991-1994 (Box 34)
  - MPC 1993-1994 (Box 34)
  - On Target's Survey 1989-1990 (Box 35)
  - NPHC 1993 (Box 35)
  - Schrieber--Research n.d. (Box 35)
  - ASAA 1988 (Box 35)
  - On Target--Center for Creative Leadership Programs (2 folders) 1989 (Box 35)
- Series VI: Associate Dean of Students,Annette Gibbs/Ronald Stump
  - Resident Staff Evaluation 1989 (Box 35)
  - Common Reading Experience Discussion 1989 (Box 35)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1973-1983 (Box 35)
  - Common Reading Experience Evaluation 1988 (Box 35)
  - Orientation--Common Experience 1989 (Box 35)
  - Common Reading Experience 1988 (Box 35)
  - Discussion Leaders Evaluation 1989 (Box 35)
  - Common Reading Experience 1990 (Box 36)
  - Common Reading Experience Discussion Sites 1990 (Box 36)
  - Suggested Books, Short Stories, Poems or Essays and Articles 1990 (Box 36)
  - Common Reading Experience 1991 (Box 36)
  - Common Reading Experience Readings 1991 (Box 36)
  - Common Reading Experience Discussion Leaders 1991 (Box 36)
  - CRE (Common Reading Experience) Participants 1991 (Box 36)
  - CRE (Common Reading Experience) Evaluations 1991 (Box 36)
  - Common Reading Experience Evaluation 1991 (Box 36)
  - Common Reading Experience (3 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 36)
  - Common Reading Experience Discussion Leaders 1990 (Box 36)
  - Composite Orientation Schedule for First Year Transfer and Grad/Prof Students 1990 (Box 36)
  - Orientation 1986 (Box 36)
  - Counseling Center 1974-1987 (Box 36)
  - Jefferson Society 1988 (Box 36)
  - Orientation 1989 (Box 36)
  - Orientation Brochures 1986 (Box 37)
  - Orientation Brochure Requisitions 1989 (Box 37)
  - Orientation (2 folders) 1986-1991 (Box 37)
  - Orientation Planning 1986 (Box 37)
  - Orientation Evaluation 1986 (Box 37)
  - Orientation Distribution List 1987 (Box 37)
  - Orientation 1990 (Box 37)
  - Convocation 1990 (Box 37)
  - Peabody/Newcomb Space Appeals Committee 1983 (Box 37)
  - President's Retreat 1985 (Box 37)
  - President's Retreat Evaluation 1986 (Box 37)
  - President's Retreat Evaluation 1986 (Box 37)
  - Student Legal Services 1984-1990 (Box 38)
  - Student Legal Services 1985-1988 (Box 38)
  - Student Legal Services 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - Student Legal Services 1974-1978 (Box 38)
  - Approval Process for Serving Alcohol at UVA Events 1990 (Box 38)
  - Arts Report, Future of the Arts atthe University of Virginia 1992 (Box 38)
  - Apartheid Simulation 1990 (Box 39)
  - Awakening, The 1988 (Box 39)
  - Documents related to the Cavalier Daily's Staff receiving salaries from SAF Funds 1990 (Box 39)
  - Biennial Evaluation and Planning 1986 (Box 39)
  - Black Student Alliance 1989 (Box 39)
  - Black Greek Affairs Roundtable 1990 (Box 39)
  - Consortium of University Publications 1985 (Box 39)
  - Contact Program 1987 (Box 39)
  - Culturfest 1989 (Box 39)
  - Cultural and Race Educators 1987 (Box 39)
  - Common Reading Experience 1993 (Box 39)
  - Common Reading Experience at Harvard 1993 (Box 39)
  - Dining Services and Outside Catering 1990 (Box 39)
  - Dining Services Program Agreement 1988 (Box 39)
  - Dining Services--Student Disruptions 1989 (Box 39)
  - Educational Programming Fair 1992 (Box 39)
  - Educational Programming Fair--Evaluations 1992 (Box 39)
  - Educational Programming Fair 1990 (Box 39)
  - Charlottesville Student Information Project 1989 (Box 39)
  - Nelson Chow Award 1989 (Box 39)
  - Common Reading Experience 1976 (Box 39)
  - First Year Focus 1991 (Box 39)
  - First Year House Councils 1993 (Box 39)
  - First Year Seminar 1990 (Box 40)
  - First Year Players 1988 (Box 40)
  - First Year Poster 1989 (Box 40)
  - Guidelines for Acknowledging Corporate Support for Activities 1988 (Box 40)
  - Jossey-Bass, Inc. Publishers 1986 (Box 40)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi Alleged Hazing (Restricted) 1993 (Box 40)
  - Korea Awareness Week 1992 (Box 40)
  - Multicultural Session, First Year Focus 1989 (Box 40)
  - Multiethnic Awareness Forum 1985 (Box 40)
  - Registration Refreshments 1992 (Box 40)
  - Parents' Orientation Panel 1992 (Box 40)